Lesson 20. Bob gets an angry call from Carol.
Carol calls Bob to tell him that a customer found a hair in her cookie. Bob wants Carol
to forget about this, but Carol thinks it's very serious. She refuses to buy any more
cookies from Bob. Bob, a lady came into the village market today,
ranting and raving. Oh yeah, what happened? She found a blue hair in her chocolate chip cookie.
Aha. I can see how she'd be taken aback. Does anybody in your family have blue hair?
As a matter of fact, my son's girlfriend Amber has blue hair. Bob, I can't sell your cookies anymore.
Aren't you blowing things out of proportion? The health department would throw
the book at me if they found out about this. Couldn't we just sweep this under the rug?
No, this is too serious. But I was just getting a handle on the cookie business. Now what would I do?
I don't have any other way of making a living. My heart goes out to you, Bob,
but you need to get your act together. I want to sell chocolate chip cookies, not hair cookies.
I guess I just knocked myself out for the past week for nothing.
Clearly.